Rob Sonter

IT TEAM LEADER - 3+ YEARS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

SharePoint / Office365
Workflow & Process Management
Microsoft PowerPlatform
Mobile Device Management
HTML5 / CSS
JavaScript
Asset Management
Project Management
Agile principles
System Development
Leadership & Management

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team player Adaptable & flexible Great communication Strategic thinking Fast learner Motivated

CONTACT

M: 0499 766 283

E: robert.sonter@yahoo.com.au

LinkedIn: robsonter91

GitHub: WrldTrvlr91

REFERENCES

AVAILABLE ON REQUEST

PROFILE

Dedicated IT professional with 3+ years experience leading both development and support teams within the not for profit sector. One of my greatest passions is working with like minded teams to develop, design and deploy solutions which improve the quality of service and care provided to its customers.

EXPERIENCE

IT TEAM LEADER

Safe Places for Children | June 2017 - Current

- Managed a team of Help Desk technicians supporting 700+ employees
- Leading a small group of BA's across core business functions
- Development of custom solutions to meet client requirements spanning a multitude of platforms and technologies
- Procurement and Asset Management of all IT equipment
- Enterprise Telecommunication contract management
- Writing and updating policies, processes and user guides
- System and Licence Administration
- Developed and maintained effective relationships with all providers and stakeholders

RESIDENTIAL SUPPORT WORKER

Autism Association WA | May 2016 - June 2017

- Provide support, care and advocacy for children and adults with Autism.
- Work with the client's family to ensure that the client meets outcomes and goals set.
- Implement positive behaviour support plans
- Support client to complete daily activities
- Support client and family to meet individual goals

CHILDREN SERVICES TEAM LEADER

House with no Steps - QLD | Feb 2012 - Mar 2016

- Manage, grow and lead a supportive team of 30+ employees
- Implement change and innovation to ensure growth and retention
- Develop person centered positive behaviour support plans
- Support and encourage at risk youth to access services
- Engage youth in educational and social programs
- Department Contract Management

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION MANAGER

Woolworths LTD - QLD | 2006 - 2012

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT BOOT CAMP

University of Western Australia | Graduate 2021

DIPLOMA BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

TAFE QLD | 2007